Guide to the E. E. Wilson Photographic Collection circa 1855-1953
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
E. E. Wilson Photographic Collection
circa 1855-1953
circa 1890-1930
Wilson, E. E. (Eddy Elbridge), 1869-1961.
P 101
2.00 cubic feet including more than 1700 photographic images 28 boxes
Special Collections and Archives Research Center 121 The Valley Library Oregon State University Corvallis, OR, 97331-4501 Phone: 541-737-2075 Email: scarc@oregonstate.edu Web: http://scarc.library.oregonstate.edu/findingaids
The E. E. Wilson Photographic Collection consists of images of Wilson, a Corvallis native and Oregon Agricultural College (OAC) alum, as well as his family and friends, the OAC campus, Corvallis, and other locations around the Pacific Northwest. The collection also includes images of the 1915 Panama Pacific Exposition in San Francisco and photos of Siletz tribe members. Digitized images from the E.E. Wilson Photographic Collection can be viewed in Oregon Digital.
Biographical Note:
Alumnus E.E. (Eddy Elbridge) Wilson was born in Corvallis in 1869 and lived there until his death in 1961. He attended Oregon Agricultural College and graduated in 1889 with the first class from the new campus. He received a law degree from the University of Oregon in 1893 and practiced law in Corvallis from then until 1925, when he became President of the First National Bank of Corvallis.
Wilson served on the Oregon Agricultural College Board of Regents for 2 terms, 1906-1915 and 1925-1929, and was treasurer of the Memorial Union Board of Governors from its founding in 1925 until his death in 1961. He was a pioneer in game preservation and member of the State Game Commission for 14 years. Wilson was an only child and never married. Wilson Hall on the OSU campus and the E. E. Wilson Wildlife Refuge north of Corvallis bear his name.
Fulton, John, 1868-1953.; Gardner, W. S.; Goldson, L.
Panama-Pacific International Exposition (1915: San Francisco, Calif.)
Albumen prints.; Ambrotypes (photographs).; Cartes-de-visite (card photographs).; Daguerreotypes (photographs).; Glass plate negatives.; Nitrate negatives.; Photographic prints.; Postcards.; Tintypes (prints).
Coast Ranges; Corvallis (Or.); Crater Lake National Park (Or.); Marys Peak (Or.); Newport (Or.); Yaquina Bay (Or.)
Wilson, E. E. (Eddy Elbridge), 1869-1961.; Wilson, Lewis Fenton, 1836-1927; Wilson, Rose, 1850-1938
Boats and boating--Oregon.; Camping--Oregon.; Coasts--Oregon.; College buildings--Oregon--Corvallis.; College students--Oregon--Corvallis.; Fishing--Oregon.; Hiking--Oregon.; Hunting--Oregon.; Outdoor recreation--Oregon.; Siletz Indians.
Colleges and Universities; National Parks; Sports and Recreation; Oregon; California; Corvallis; Photographs
The bulk of the E. E. Wilson Photographic Collection was likely transferred to the University Archives in the 1960s. Additional photographs were transferred from the E. E. Wilson Papers to this collection in 1999. The collection now resides in the Special Collections and Archives Research Center.
This collection is open for research.
The E. E. Wilson Papers (MSS WilsonEE) contain materials pertaining to Wilson's personal and professional activities including his involvement with the Board of Regents, Memorial Union Board of Governors, and the State Game Commission. Images of Wilson can be found in Harriet's Photograph Collection (P HC).
The Special Collections and Archives Research Center holdings include numerous photograph collections featuring images of the Oregon State University campus (Beaver Yearbook Photographs (P 003) and the Buildings Photographic Collection (P 016)), Corvallis (Corvallis, Oregon, Photograph Collection (P 051)), and outdoor scenery and recreation (Mount Hood Area Excursion Photograph Album (P310) and the Lewis Lucy Scrapbook (MSS Lewis).
The E.E. Wilson Photographic Collection is comprised of nine series: 1. Agriculture and Industry, circa 1890-1910; 2. City and Town Life, circa 1867-1950; 3. Events, circa 1900-1953; 4. Oregon Agricultural College, circa 1890-1950; 5. Oregon Coast, circa 1890-1920; 6. Outdoor Recreation and Nature Scenes, circa 1890-1945; 7. People, circa 1855-1953; 8. Souvenir Views of British Columbia and Alaska, 1915.
Materials are described topically by series and alphabetically by title within each series. Items are physically arranged by format and thereunder numerically. Items can be requested by the item number (such as P101:003).
This personal collection of photographs assembled by E.E. Wilson includes images of Wilson, his family, and friends; the Oregon Agricultural College campus and buildings; Corvallis homes and businesses, including the Carriage Factory and the Opera House; the Panama Pacific Exposition in San Francisco (1915); wildlife and outdoor scenes; outdoor recreation including camping, hunting, fishing, and hiking; and Native Americans (Siletz). Many different photographers are represented. Some of the 1890s images of Oregon Agricultural College were taken by John Fulton; there are portraits from many different studios in Corvallis (including L. Goldson and W. S. Gardner), Albany, Portland and outside Oregon.
This collection includes a variety of forms, but consists predominantly of black and white prints, many of which have accompanying original glass and or nitrate negatives. The glass negatives include 315 4x5 plates, 161 5x7 plates, and 6 5x8 plates. Other notable formats include several ambrotypes, daguerrotypes, tintypes, and cyanotypes. Many of the prints are mounted.
Materials are described topiccally by series and alphabetically by title within each series. Items are physically arranged by format and thereunder numerically. Items can be requested by the item number (such as P101:003).
- Agriculture and Industry, circa 1890-1910; Series 1
  Series 1 is comprised of photographs of mills, farms, orchards, livestock, and other agricultural and industrial work. Of particular note are several photographs documenting late-19th century hopyards.
  - Chicks in a hat, P101:0032
    1 5x7 glass negative
  - Corvallis Carriage Wagon Factory, circa 1900; P101:0443a
    Digitized image available in Oregon Digital.
    1 photographic print; 1 4x5 glass negative
  - Corvallis Carriage Wagon Factory, circa 1900; P101:0443b
    2 photographic prints
  - Cow, P101:0808a
    1 4x5 glass negative
  - Cow in pasture in front of house, circa 1910; P101:1087b
  - Farmhouse, circa 1905; P101:1134
    1 photographic print
  - Fenced pasture, farm in background, circa 1910; P101:0915
  - Flax mill, circa 1890; P101:0840
  - Groves Carding Mill, circa 1890s; P101:0449
  - Hen and baby chicks, P101:0033
  - Hen and baby chicks, P101:0034
  - Hen and baby chicks, P101:0035
  - Hillside orchard [?], circa 1900; P101:0914a
  - Hop pickers at W.E. Thorton hopyard, North Yakima, Washington, circa 1890; P101:0465
  - Hop picking at W.E. Thorton hopyard, North Yakima, Washington, circa 1890; P101:0464a
    Digitized images available in Oregon Digital.
  - Hop picking at W.E. Thorton hopyard, North Yakima, Washington, circa 1890; P101:0464b
  - Houses and outbuildings at base of clearcut hill, P101:1040
  - Mint still, circa 1900; P101:0841
  - Native American hop pickers, Moxee Valley, Yakima, Washington, circa 1895; P101:0177
    1 photographic print (carte de visite)
  - Pigs suckling, P101:0031
  - Plowed field with piles of plant material, circa 1910; P101:0917
  - Plowed field with piles of plant material, circa 1910; P101:0918
  - View of fence and farm outbuildings, circa 1905; P101:1296
  - View of Wilson farm [?], P101:1297
  - Willamette River and Fisher's Mill, P101:0185
  - Willamette Valley farm, circa 1900; P101:1090a
- City and Town Life, circa 1867-1950; Series 2
  Series 2 includes images of homes, schools, retail businesses, and other public and private buildings. The series also includes images of street scenes, home interiors, and community events and activities. Though many of these images appear to be from Corvallis and nearby locations, there are also photographs of California missions, a school in England, and a home in Nebraska.
  - "Some of Bradley & Rulofson's Babies," San Francisco (publicity photo), circa 1885; P101:1247
  - Allen home, 3rd and C Street, Corvallis, Oregon, P101:0182
  - Automobiles, circa 1915; P101:1263
    1 nitrate negative
  - Automobiles, circa 1915; P101:1264
  - Automobiles, circa 1915; P101:1265a
  - Boy in E.E. Wilson's law office, circa 1900; P101:0804a
  - Cafeteria and shop, P101:0863
  - Calday Grange Grammar School, West Kirby, England with Hollowell (headmaster), wife, and children, circa 1890; P101:0475
  - Callahan estate document, 1915; P101:0260
    2 photographic prints; 2 4x5 negatives
  - Cats on porch, circa 1900; P101:0029
  - Cats on porch, circa 1900; P101:0030
  - Corvallis public school, 6th grade, circa 1905; P101:0595
  - Dining table decorated with roses, circa 1900; P101:0638b
    3 photographic prints; 1 4x5 glass negative
  - Edgecomb home in Omaha, Nebraska, 1924; P101:0839
  - Elk City, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:1091
  - Elk City, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:1099
  - Elk Hotel, P101:1262
  - Five women on bridge at Oak Creek, circa 1900; P101:0187
  - Foundations of Camp Adair buildings, circa 1950; P101:1306
    4 photographic prints
  - Group with auto in front of service garage, circa 1915; P101:1248b
    2 photographic prints; 1 nitrate negative
  - Group with auto in front of service garage, circa 1915; P101:1248c
    1 photographic print; 1 nitrate negative
  - Home of A. Rennie in snow, North 2nd Street, Corvallis, Oregon, circa 1920; P101:0458
  - Home of Hout family, circa 1890; P101:0459
  - Home of Kirkpatricks at 6th and Madison, Corvallis, Oregon., circa 1895; P101:0347
  - Home of Lewis family, 1890; P101:0442
  - Home of Sam Wyatt on North D Street, Philomath, Oregon, circa 1910; P101:0323
  - Horse and sleigh, circa 1915; P101:1267
  - House exterior with garden area, circa 1900; P101:0639a
  - House exterior, child sitting on steps, circa 1900; P101:0638c
  - House interior, P101:0639b
  - House on 1st Street, Corvallis, Oregon, circa 1890; P101:0864
  - Iris, P101:0001
  - Iris, P101:0009
  - J.A. Knight Furniture Store on NE corner of 2nd and Monroe Streets, Corvallis, Oregon, circa 1870; P101:0448
    Digitized image in Oregon Digital.
  - Johnson House, circa 1930; P101:0262
    2 nitrate negatives
  - Johnson House, circa 1930; P101:0264
  - Johnson House, circa 1930; P101:0265
  - Johnson House, circa 1930; P101:0266
  - Man and woman in house, circa 1900; P101:0667
  - Map of Corvallis, Oregon, circa 1890; P101:0445
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0189
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0190
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0191
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0192
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0193
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0195
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0196
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0197
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0198
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0199
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0200
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0201
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0202
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0203
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0204
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0205
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0206
  - Mission, California, circa 1930; P101:0207
  - Mission, San Diego, California, circa 1930; P101:0194
  - Myers family home, 1938; P101:0624
    1 acetate negative
  - Nasturtiums, circa 1910; P101:0016
  - Nasturtiums in basket on mantle, P101:0013
  - Opera House, SW corner of 4th and Madison, Corvallis, Oregon, P101:0184
  - Oregon National Guard, May 31, 1898; P101:0596
  - Palace Hotel, San Francisco (photo of drawing), circa 1890; P101:1238
  - People standing by automobile, P101:125b
  - Piano with flowers on top, circa 1900; P101:0640a
  - Piano with flowers on top, circa 1900; P101:0640b
  - Piano with flowers on top, circa 1900; P101:0640c
  - Presbyterian Church, Corvallis, Oregon, circa 1867; P101:1328
  - Roman coin, P101:0620
  - Roses, P101:0015
  - Roses in a basket, P101:0011a
  - Roses in a basket, P101:0011b
  - Roses in a basket, P101:0012
  - Roses in a basket, P101:0014
  - Sightseeing bus, San Francisco (chain driven vehicle), circa 1910; P101:1261
  - Three photographs mounted on wall, circa 1900; P101:0713
  - Tree in front yard of house, circa 1910; P101:0861
  - Unidentified building, P101:0271
  - Unidentified home, P101:0270
  - Unidentified house, circa 1900; P101:0852
  - Unidentified house, circa 1910; P101:0860
  - Unidentified house, P101:0623
    4 photographic prints; 1 4x5 glass negative
  - Unidentified house in Craftsmen barn style, circa 1910; P101:0856
  - Unidentified house on river, circa 1910; P101:0858
  - Unidentified two story house, P101:0855
  - View of house from High Street showing big oak tree; also the elevation of rock dividing the lot, circa 1910; P101:0473
  - Wilson and Withycombe houses, P101:0514
  - Wilson family home, circa 1900; P101:0520
  - Wilson family home, circa 1900; P101:0524
  - Wilson family home, circa 1900; P101:0611
  - Wilson family home, circa 1900; P101:0850
  - Wilson family home, circa 1910; P101:0612
  - Wilson family home, circa 1910; P101:0613
  - Wilson family home, circa 1910; P101:0614
  - Wilson family home, circa 1910; P101:0615
  - Wilson family home, circa 1910; P101:0616
    1 photographic print; 1 4x5 glass negative; 1 nitrate negative
  - Wilson family home, circa 1910; P101:0617
  - Wilson family home, circa 1910; P101:0641a
  - Wilson family home, circa 1920; P101:0636a
  - Wilson family home, P101:0515
  - Wilson family home, P101:0626a
  - Wilson family home, P101:0626b
  - Wilson family home, Oak Creek, Corvallis, Oregon, circa 1905; P101:0610a
    1 4x5 glass negative; 1 nitrate negative
  - Wilson family home--arch trellis, circa 1920; P101:0636b
  - Wilson family home--backyard, P101:0633
  - Wilson family home--bedroom, P101:0637b
  - Wilson family home--fireplace, P101:0637a
  - Wilson family home--fireplace, P101:0638a
    1 photographic print; 2 nitrate negatives
  - Wilson family home--fish pool, P101:0635
  - Wilson family home--in snow, circa 1900; P101:0518
  - Wilson family home--in snow, circa 1900; P101:0519
  - Wilson family home--in snow, circa 1900; P101:0521
  - Wilson family home--in snow, circa 1900; P101:0522
  - Wilson family home--in snow, circa 1900; P101:0523
  - Wilson family home--in snow, P101:0625a
    4 photographic prints; 1 nitrate negative
  - Wilson family home--in snow, P101:0625b
  - Wilson family home--rose bush, P101:0632a
  - Wilson family home--wisteria, P101:0627
  - Wilson family home--wisteria, P101:0628
  - Wilson family home--wisteria, P101:0629
  - Wilson family home--wisteria, P101:0630
  - Wilson, E.E., Rose, and others on porch of house, P101:1300
  - Wisteria at home of Lewis F. Wilson [?], circa 1910; P101:0485
- Events, circa 1900-1953; Series 3
  Series 3 is comprised of photographs of various events and activities including birthday parties, theatrical productions, and a 1953 banquet honoring E.E. Wilson. The series also includes numerous photographs from the 1915 Panama Pacific Exposition and photographs of members of the Siletz tribe participating in a 1910 Independence Day celebration.
  - "Clinton's birthday", October 1, 1912; P101:0857
    1 photographic print (postcard)
  - A.B. Smith birthday party, Aero Club, May 1, 1953; P101:1312
  - A.B. Smith birthday party, Aero Club, May 1, 1953; P101:1313
  - A.B. Smith birthday party, Aero Club, May 1, 1953; P101:1314
  - A.B. Smith birthday party, Aero Club, May 1, 1953; P101:1315
  - A.B. Smith birthday party, Aero Club, May 1, 1953; P101:1316
  - A.B. Smith birthday party, Aero Club, May 1, 1953; P101:1317
  - A.B. Smith birthday party, Aero Club, May 1, 1953; P101:1318
  - A.B. Smith birthday party, Aero Club, May 1, 1953; P101:1319
  - A.B. Smith birthday party, Aero Club, May 1, 1953; P101:1320
  - Banquet in honor of E.E. Wilson, circa 1953; P101:0477
  - Banquet in honor of E.E. Wilson, circa 1953; P101:0478
  - Banquet in honor of E.E. Wilson, circa 1953; P101:0479
  - Banquet in honor of E.E. Wilson, circa 1953; P101:0480
  - Banquet in honor of E.E. Wilson, circa 1953; P101:0481
  - Cast of a play, circa 1900; P101:0505
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0528
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0529
    1 4x5 glass negative; 1 acetate negative
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0530
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0531
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0532
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0533
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0534a
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0534b
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0534c
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0535a
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0535b
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0536
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0537
  - Minstrel show, circa 1905; P101:0538
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0156
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0157
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0158
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0159
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0160
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0161
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0162
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0163
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0164
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0165
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0166
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0167
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0168
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0169
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0170
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0171
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0172
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0173
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0174
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0175
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0176
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0279
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0280
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0281
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0282
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0283
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0284
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0285
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0286
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0287
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0289
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0290
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0291
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0292
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0293
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0294
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0298
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0299
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0300
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0301
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0302
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0303
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0304
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0305
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0306
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0307
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0308
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0309
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0310
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0312
  - Panama Pacific Exposition, 1915; P101:0313
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Battleships in San Francisco Bay [?], 1915; P101:0111
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Birds in plaza, 1915; P101:0101
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Buildings and statues, 1915; P101:0114
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Fountain, 1915; P101:0099
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Fountain, 1915; P101:0118
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Fountains and statues, 1915; P101:0112
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Fountains and statues, 1915; P101:0113
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0106
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0107
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0108
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0109
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0110
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0119
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0120
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0121
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0122
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0123
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0124
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts, 1915; P101:0125b
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts statuary, 1915; P101:0096
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts statuary, 1915; P101:0097
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts statuary, 1915; P101:0098
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts statuary, 1915; P101:0115
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts statuary, 1915; P101:0116
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Palace of Fine Arts statuary, 1915; P101:0117
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--San Francisco Bay [?], 1915; P101:0105
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0126
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0127
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0128
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0129
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0130
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0131
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0132
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0133
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0134
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0135
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0136
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0137
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0138
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0139
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0140
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0141
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0142
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0143
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0144
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0145
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0146
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0147
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0148
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0149
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0150
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0151
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0152
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0153
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Souvenir photographs, 1915; P101:0154
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Statue, 1915; P101:0100
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Statue of nude, 1915; P101:0155
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Statues and fountains, 1915; P101:0102
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Statues and fountains, 1915; P101:0103
  - Panama Pacific Exposition--Statues and fountains, 1915; P101:0104
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0453d
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0453e
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0453f
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0453g
    1 photographic print 1 nitrate negative